http://www.musicarussica.com/p/policies

CDs/DVDs
CDs HOME PAGE
VIEW ALL CDS and DVDS
Russian Sacred Choral Anthologies (Mixed Voices)
Choral Music from the Balkans, the Caucasus, and Baltics
Russian Secular Choral Music (Mixed Voices)
Russian and Other Slavic Folklore (Field Recordings)
MP3 Collections
Russian Choral Folk Music
Russian Popular and Instrumental Music
Videos (DVDs)
Women's/Treble Voices
Christmas Carols (Mixed)
Women's/Treble Voices
PROMOTIONAL PACKETS (50% off)
Pricing
All prices and charges are in US Dollars. Prices are subject to change without notice.
Shipping Policy
Your order will be sent via US Postal Service or UPS, based upon the size and weight of your order and whether you selected an expedited shipping method.
Orders are usually shipped within 3-5 business days.
Shipping rates are calculated in real time based on the shipping options you select, the weight of the selected products, and the destination. A handling fee will be added to the shipping charges.
Musica Russica does not ship on weekends or holidays. Shipping times will vary depending on the shipping method, location, and the availability of product.
Orders for requested next day delivery must be received by 10:00am PST.
Orders shipped via UPS require a physical address, as UPS will not deliver to a PO Box. All orders to PO Boxes will be shipped via US Postal Service.
International Orders
Recipient is responsible for all customs fees and duties associated with the order for international shipments. Check with your respective local authorities concerning any applicable taxes, duties, and/or potential customs delays. Musica Russica is not responsible for any of these fees or delays.
Return Policy
Musica Russica, Inc. is committed to provide our customers with quality merchandise. Upon receiving your order, please inspect it at once to confirm accurate receipt of goods, to detect possible missing items, or damaged merchandise.
Returns must be made within (30) days of order invoice date.
Merchandise may not be returned without prior authorization and approval from Musica Russica. Unauthorized returns will not be accepted.
CDs and DVDs must be new and unopened, and returned in their original shrink-wrap packaging.
Sheet music and books must be new and unused. Please note that the following conditions of return are unacceptable: sticker marks (from price labels, or otherwise), bent corners or creases, pen or pencil markings of any sort in the sheet music, bends or dents on the good(s).
Please wrap your return items carefully using ample packaging materials so that goods are not damaged in transit. Returns received in damaged condition will not be accepted or eligible for credit or refund.
Be sure to include a copy of your packing invoice and mail it to:
Musica Russica, Inc.
Attn: Returns
7925 Silverton Ave
Suite 501
San Diego, CA 92126
USA
Refund Policy
Musica Russica will issue a refund or credit to your account once your authorized return is received and inspected at our warehouse. Credit card purchases will be refunded to your credit card. Check purchases may be refunded by check or by applying a credit to your account. Returned products must be in original condition and in the original packaging. Freight charges are not refundable unless the return is due to a defect or Musica Russica error.
Privacy Policy
Musica Russica, Inc. owns the Musica Russica website and business. Musica Russica is committed to protecting your privacy. By visiting our website you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.
Information We Collect & How it is Used
Musica Russica, Inc. does NOT sell, trade or rent your personal information to others. To process your order, we require you to provide your name, mailing address, credit card number, CVC code, and card expiration date. When you sign up for our email newsletter, catalogs, or other information, we request your name and an email address. We monitor customer traffic patterns and site usage to help us develop our web design and layout. We may also use your contact information to notify you about important changes to our site, new services and special offers. If you would rather not receive this information, you may opt out at any time.
Protection & Security of Customer Information
When you place an order with Musica Russica, your personal information and credit card information is safe. This is because we have taken steps to ensure a secure and superior shopping environment. We use state-of-the-art secure socket layer (SSL) encryption technology that protects the transmission of your credit card information.
Links on our Website to Other Businesses
We are not responsible for the privacy practices of any other website. We encourage our customers to read the privacy policies of each website they enter. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by Musica Russica.
Notification of Changes
If we decide to make a material change to our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement. Our goal is to keep customers aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we disclose it. Your trust and loyalty is one of our most important assets and we take this very seriously.
Feedback
Musica Russica welcomes your questions and comments about our privacy policy. Our business continues to evolve rapidly and consumer trust is an important element for that growth. Please email us. You may also contact us by mail:
Musica Russica, Inc.
